University Advancement Division Records UA043
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
University Advancement Division Records
1857 -- 2017
1980 -- 2014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Development and Alumni Relations
University Advancement Division
UA043
17.5 Linear Feet 11 record cartons, 5 letter size document boxes, 5 half letter size document boxes, 1 legal size document box
30 Digital Object(s)
This collection documents the Division of University Advancement's fundraising activities. Materials include promotional documents, development and fundraising plans, reports, publications, and audiovisual materials.
Arrangement
This collection is organized in seven series: Administrative records; Communications and marketing materials; Development research; Funded projects; Fundraising materials; Special events records; and Audiovisual materials.; and Born-digital materials.
Custodial History
Collection formerly called "Office of Development"
Scope and Contents
This collection contains administrative and marketing records from the Department of University Advancement. Materials include promotional documents, development and fundraising plans, reports, and publications, as well as audiovisual materials and microfilm. Material in this collection ranges from 1857-2017, with the majority of material dating from 1980-2014.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Biographical / Historical
The division of University Advancement oversees fundraising, alumni relations, and donor relations for Tufts University (Tufts University Fact Book 2017-2018). University Advancement has its roots in the mid-1970s expansion of the Resources division, when the division began to focus on managing funds and campaigns. Previously, external relations and fundraising had been overseen by different departments in a more ad hoc manner. By 1976, a Director of Fundraising had been hired under the Vice-President of Resources (Tufts University Fact Book 1976-1977). In 1978, the Development division was created, which oversaw alumni, community, and government relations and included a budget officer (Tufts University Fact Book 1978-1979). The following year, in 1979, the department was renamed University Development and continued to grow with the creation of new positions and reorganizations of department hierarchies (Tufts University Fact Book 1979-1980). In 2003, the division changed its name to University Advancement (Tufts University Fact Book 2003-2004).
Advancement; Alumni and Alumni Relations; Curriculum and Instruction -- Scholarships, Fellowships, Awards
- Administrative records and reports, 1857 -- 2011; 1950 -- 1990; UA043.001; 5.72 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains a variety of administrative records concerning alumni relations and fundraising, including development plans, project outlines, reports, accreditation manuals, marketing materials, and correspondence. Most records in this series concern the planning and development of specific fundraising projects in the second half of the twentieth century, such as the Second Century Fund, the Annual Fund, and the Engineering Building Fund. A significant portion of this series contains monthly progress reports on the Campaign for Tufts in the 1980s. A notable folder in this series is dedicated to Black alumni. Materials date from 1857-2011, with the majority dating from 1950-1990.
  Arrangement
  Boxes 1-6 in this series preserve their received arrangement. Boxes 7 and 8 are organized chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
  - General, 1971 -- 1980; UA043.001.001.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Open for research.
  - Black alumni, 1965 -- 1973; UA043.001.001.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    75 years from date of creation.
  - Case statement draft, 1980 October; UA043.001.001.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Communications office, 1944 -- 1993; UA043.001.001.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Film records, 1954 -- 1966; UA043.001.001.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Greek studies, 1959 -- 1960; UA043.001.001.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - TV and radio, 1958 -- 1972; UA043.001.001.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University communications Chase Report, 1961 April; UA043.001.001.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - University development plan 1980, 1980 January; UA043.001.002.00001; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Fund raising general, 1878 -- 1976; UA043.001.002.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund general, 1857 -- 1975; UA043.001.002.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund 1956, circa 1956; UA043.001.002.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund 1957, circa 1956 -- 1957; UA043.001.002.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund 1958, circa 1957 -- 1958; UA043.001.002.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund 1959, circa 1958 -- 1959; UA043.001.002.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising brochures, circa 1911 -- 1978; UA043.001.003.00001; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund 1960, circa 1959 -- 1960; UA043.001.003.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund 1961, circa 1960 -- 1961; UA043.001.003.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund 1962, circa 1961 -- 1963; UA043.001.003.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund 1963, circa 1962 -- 1963; UA043.001.003.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund 1967-72, 1967 -- 1972; UA043.001.003.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund class agents, circa 1960 -- 1967; UA043.001.003.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Fund raising Annual Fund publicity, circa 1970 -- 1973; UA043.001.003.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Fund raising Jumbo Bond Campaign, 1922 -- 1924; UA043.001.003.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Fund raising TUP publicity, 1961 -- 1963; UA043.001.004.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Fund raising Centennial Fund, circa 1946 -- 1947; UA043.001.004.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Fund raising Engineering Building Fund, 1956 -- 1963; UA043.001.004.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fund raising President's Day, 1962 -- 1964; UA043.001.004.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fund raising Second Century Fund, 1950 -- 1955; UA043.001.004.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 5, Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Fund raising Silvanus Packard Society, 1972 -- 1974, 1992; UA043.001.005.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Fund raising Sustaining Fund, 1926 March; UA043.001.005.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Fund raising Tufts Foundation, 1918 -- 1935; UA043.001.005.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Fund raising TUP general, 1960 -- 1963; UA043.001.005.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fund raising TUP correspondence and memos, 1960 -- 1963; UA043.001.005.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fund raising TUP major gifts, 1961 May -- December; UA043.001.005.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fund raising TUP reports, circa 1960 -- 1961; UA043.001.005.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Fund raising TUP Steering Committee, 1960 -- 1963; UA043.001.006.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Government resources, 1971 -- 1977; UA043.001.006.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Final report on nontraditional sources of support for TUSVM, 1977 October; UA043.001.007.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - TUSVM accreditation manual, 1977 March; UA043.001.007.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Report on establishing a school of veterinary medicine, 1977 February; UA043.001.007.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Research Service Laboratory proposal, circa 1977; UA043.001.007.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Report on the Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1972 September; UA043.001.007.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Financial projections for TUSVM report, 1978 March; UA043.001.007.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - TUSVM accreditation manual, 1979 November; UA043.001.007.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Memos on TUSVM financial forecast, 1978 January; UA043.001.007.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Veterinary School Feasibility Study materials, circa 1977 May; UA043.001.007.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Communications Planning report, 1979 November; UA043.001.007.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Large Animal Clinical Facility design submission, 1977 September; UA043.001.007.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - The Campaign for Tufts development plan, 1980 November; UA043.001.007.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - A Historical Review of Grants and Contracts at Tufts, circa 1979; UA043.001.007.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - University development plan, circa 1979; UA043.001.007.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Richard Kimball development files, circa 1954 -- 2001; UA043.001.007.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Donor relations materials and CD, 2007 -- 2011; UA043.001.007.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Monthly progress reports, 1983 October -- 1990 March; UA043.001.008; 28 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 1-28)
  - Fund raising Capital Campaign white paper, 1975; UA043.001.SB147.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box Shared 147, Folder 5)
- Communications and marketing materials, 2008 -- 2017; UA043.002; 2.64 Linear Feet
  This series contains marketing materials related to a variety of fundraising projects and events, including invitations, call for donations, fliers, and magazines (mostly the Tufts Blueprint). The types of material in this series overlaps with Special events records and Fundraising materials. Communications and marketing materials, however, tend to be broader in scope than Special events records and more concerned with promotional material. A notable type of record in this series is a list of the promotional content created by University Advancement during a given fiscal year. Each project is assigned a number and these numbers are then printed or written on most of the materials. Materials date from 2008-2017.
  The organization of this series preserves its received arrangement. For each fiscal year, there is a record of the promotional content created by University Advancement in which each project is assigned a number. Up to the 2013 fiscal year, the material is organized by project number in descending order.
  This series is open for research.
  - 2009 fiscal year projects record, 2008 -- 2009; UA043.002.009.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 2008 -- 2009, UA043.002.009.00002; 3 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 2-4)
  - 2010 fiscal year projects record, 2009 -- 2010; UA043.002.009.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 2009 -- 2010, UA043.002.009.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 2010, UA043.002.009.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 2009 -- 2010, UA043.002.009.00006; 4 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 8-11)
  - 2009 -- 2011, UA043.002.009.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 2009 -- 2010, UA043.002.009.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - circa 2009 -- 2010, UA043.002.009.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 2011 fiscal year projects record, 2010 -- 2011; UA043.002.009.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - circa 2010 -- 2011, UA043.002.009.00011; 5 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 16-20, Box 10, Folder 1-5)
  - 2013 fiscal year projects record, 2012 -- 2013; UA043.002.010.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - circa 2012 -- 2013, UA043.002.010.00002; 5 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 7-11)
  - 2014 fiscal year projects record, 2013 -- 2014; UA043.002.010.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - circa 2013 -- 2014, UA043.002.010.00004; 8 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 13-20)
  - 2015 fiscal year projects record, 2014 -- 2015; UA043.002.011.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - circa 2014 -- 2015, UA043.002.011.00002; 4 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 2-5)
  - Jumbo Impact, 2017; UA043.002.011.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Distinction Awards flier, 2017; UA043.002.011.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Development research, 1984, 1999; UA043.003; 3.28 Linear Feet
  This series contains microfilm and storage disks related to donor prospect research. The microfilm dates from 1984 and the storage disks date from 1999.
  Materials in this series preserve their received arrangement.
  This series is closed for 75 years from the date of creation.
  - Microfiche cabinet development research files, 1860 -- 1990; UA043-023 (Box data_value_missing_948507f75c8b39c2ed5422d6f11863fb)
    75 years from the date of creation.
    Precise provenance of the microfiche cabinet is unclear; no accession number or record exists documenting transfer from office (most likely the research division of the development/advancement office) to Tisch Library or DCA sometime in the late 1990s or early 2000s. Nor do we know precise date of transfer. After several years of trying to ascertain provenance and after extensive discussions with University Advancement, we are cataloging the files as part of UA043. University Advancement has changed its structures repeatedly over the last years and no documentation exists regarding those internal changes. In 2012, Development general starts a file on a potential donor and then hands the file to the division of Prospect Development and Research and we can thus presume that the microfiche files were handled in an analog manner in the past. These files could thus also be processed under a collection for Prospect Development and Research should we decide to create such a collection. According to e-mail correspondence with Paula Menzel, Assoc Dir Adv Gift & Info Svcs (2009), the microfiche was most likely produced in the early 1980s prior to them using Keyfile. Apparently the original documents were then sent to a currently unknown storage facility in NH. It thus appears likely that paper records were destroyed given that they have not been billed for storage for years. When the company that produced the microfiche was contacted by the Archivist for Reference and Collections, it had no information when the microfilming was done nor what negative format was used. It is thus possible that early microfiche are made of combustible material. The date range is very imprecise; it refers to documents that might have been filmed and is based on spot checks. Individual research development files might easily include last wills, letters or newsprint that date from earlier years. The later date range of 1990 was chosen because we know that files exist containing material from the late 1980s.
  - AAA Carpets - Cole, Catherine, 1984 June 14; UA043.000317 (Box 12)
  - Aach, David L. - Adams, Vito W., 1984 March 20; UA043.000318 (Box 13)
  - Abate, Frank J. - Lamb, Ms. Edith, 1984 June 15; UA043.000319 (Box 12)
  - Abbott, Charles J. - Gontrum, David Martin, 1984 June 15; UA043.000320 (Box 12)
  - Adams, Walter D. - Ales, Andrew J., Jr., 1984 March 20; UA043.000321 (Box 13)
  - Alessa, Dr. Shamlan Y. - Altman, Dr. Lawrence K., 1984 March 20; UA043.000322 (Box 13)
  - Altman, Sondra J. - Anderson, Mrs. Herbert R., 1984 March 20; UA043.000323 (Box 13)
  - Anderson, Jane E. - Apalakian, Richard, 1984 March 20; UA043.000324 (Box 13)
  - Aparo, Salvatore J. - Arnold, Mrs. George J. (Joanne Crosby), 1984 March 20; UA043.000325 (Box 13)
  - Appli. Of Students Grad in 1983 K-Z - Appli. Of Students Grad in 1985 K-Z (cont), 1984 June 15; UA043.000326 (Box 12)
  - Appli. Of Students Grad in 1985 A-Z (cont) - (2) Medicine Class '84, '85, '83 (3) Dental '85 (4) BSOT '82, '83, '84, '85, 1984 June 15; UA043.000327 (Box 12)
  - Arnold, Dr. George L. - Atwood, Bradford B., 1984 March 20; UA043.000328 (Box 13)
  - Atwood, Mrs. Donald J. - Baglione, Dr. Frank M., 1984 March 20; UA043.000329 (Box 13)
  - Bagnalll, Dr. Melville C. - Banas, Dr. John S., Jr., 1984 March 20; UA043.000330 (Box 13)
  - Bancroft, Janet - Barr, Laural, 1984 March 23; UA043.000331 (Box 13)
  - Barr, Robert W. - Bates, Margaret L., 1984 March 23; UA043.000332 (Box 13)
  - Bates, Robert Graham - Bedell, Dr. Laurence Jr., 1984 March 23; UA043.000333 (Box 13)
  - Bedell, Robert G. - Benington, Dr. Frederick, 1984 March 23; UA043.000334 (Box 13)
  - Benis, Anthony - Bergin, Timothy, 1984 March 23; UA043.000335 (Box 13)
  - Bergkuist, David F. - Bersch, Rosemary, 1984 March 23; UA043.000336 (Box 13)
  - Bershad, Thomas - Birkby, Dr. Bruce, 1984 March 23; UA043.000337 (Box 13)
  - Birkins, Ransom P. - Blecker, Mrs. Marcia, 1984 March 23; UA043.000338 (Box 13)
  - Blecker, Robert I. - Boivin, William S., 1984 March 23; UA043.000339 (Box 13)
  - Bojar, Alvin - Bourgeois, Hector S., 1984 March 23; UA043.000340 (Box 13)
  - Bourgeois, James F. - Boyne, Philip J., 1984 March 23; UA043.000341 (Box 13)
  - Boynton, David B. - Brenneman, Dr. C. James, 1984 March 28; UA043.000342 (Box 13)
  - Brenner, Daniel S. - Brooks, Mrs. Miriam (Miriam Willis), 1984 March 28; UA043.000343 (Box 13)
  - Brooks, Philip L. - Brundage, Diane E., 1984 March 28; UA043.000344 (Box 13)
  - Bruneau, Dr. Robert J. - Burger, Robert H., 1984 April 3; UA043.000345 (Box 13)
  - Burgess, Broadway O. - Buttner, Joseph R., 1984 April 3; UA043.000346 (Box 13)
  - Buttolph, Maria L. - Campbell, Ms. Laura, 1984 April 3; UA043.000347 (Box 13)
  - Campbell, Mrs. Leverett W. 3rd (Barbara J. Bilowz) - Carpenter, Dr. Henry G. Jr., 1984 April 4; UA043.000348 (Box 13)
  - Carpenter, Jeanne A. - Castrucci, Manlio S., 1984 April 4; UA043.000349 (Box 13)
  - Casullo, Dr. Daniel P. - Charnley, Dr. Leonard R., 1984 April 4; UA043.000350 (Box 13)
  - Charnock, Robert H. - Churbuck, Kenneth E., 1984 April 4; UA043.000351 (Box 13)
  - Church, Deborah Lynn - Clasquin, Dr. Frederick H., 1984 April 4; UA043.000352 (Box 13)
  - Class of 1889 - Class of 1981, 1984 June 15; UA043.000353 (Box 12)
  - Classon, Ms. Elizabeth A. - Cohen, Mrs. Burton H. (Carole S. Levy), 1984 April 10; UA043.000354 (Box 13)
  - Cohen, Dr. Carl - Colby, Mrs. Richard, 1984 April 5; UA043.000355 (Box 13)
  - Colchamiro, Dr. Esther, K. - Conklin, Ms. Katherine M., 1984 April 5; UA043.000356 (Box 13)
  - Cole, Edward C. - Goldstein, M and M,, H., 1984 June 14; UA043.000357 (Box 12)
  - Conklin, Sarah L. Bingham - Cooper, Maj Leland J., 1984 April 10; UA043.000358 (Box 13)
  - Cooper, Leslie, M. - Costelle, Jerry, J., 1984 April 5; UA043.000359 (Box 13)
  - Costello, Mrs. Jerry J. (Nella Van Winkelen) - Crocker, Mrs. Kimball T. (Caroline M. Phillips), 1984 April 10; UA043.000360 (Box 13)
  - Crocker, Kimball T. Jr. - Currie, Andrew E., 1984 April 10; UA043.000361 (Box 13)
  - Currie, Barbara F. - Damis, Dr. John J., 1984 April 10; UA043.000362 (Box 13)
  - Damodaran, Ambady K. - Davis, William B., 1984 April 10; UA043.000363 (Box 13)
  - Davis, Dr. William C. - Delgizzi, Dr. Guido L., 1984 April 11; UA043.000364 (Box 13)
  - Delgreco, Dr. Francis P. - Desforges, Dr. Gerard, 1984 April 16; UA043.000365 (Box 13)
  - Desforges, Dr. Jane Mary - Dieterle, Mrs. Ronald (Laura Puffer), 1984 April 16; UA043.000366 (Box 13)
  - Dietrich, Mrs. Mary M. (Mary E. Miller) - Dockstrader, Bruce L., 1984 April 16; UA043.000367 (Box 13)
  - Dockstrader, Ernest K. - Donahue, William L., 1984 April 16; UA043.000368 (Box 13)
  - Donald, Susan L. - Dowse, Mrs. Edmund Jr., 1984 April 16; UA043.000369 (Box 13)
  - Dowse, Eunice M. - Dugan, Mrs. Michelle (Michelle A. Marchesano), 1984 April 16; UA043.000370 (Box 13)
  - Dugas, Gail D. - Eaton, Mrs. Barbara S., 1984 April 16; UA043.000371 (Box 13)
  - Eaton, Mrs. David J. (Constance H. Greze) - Elliot, CDR William A., 1984 April 16; UA043.000372 (Box 13)
  - Elliot, Anne M. - Erickson, Peter L., 1984 April 16; UA043.000373 (Box 13)
  - Erickson, Robert E. - Falkenham, Elwin R., 1984 April 16; UA043.000374 (Box 13)
  - Falkoff, Barry J. - Feld, Dr. Bruce, 1984 April 16; UA043.000375 (Box 13)
  - Feld, Ellen Lois - Finigan, Joseph L., 1984 April 16; UA043.000376 (Box 13)
  - Fink, Benjamin W. - Fitzgerald, Timothy J., 1984 April 16; UA043.000377 (Box 13)
  - Fitzgerald, Mrs. William Jr. - Fong, Theodore C C, 1984 April 16; UA043.000378 (Box 13)
  - Fonstad, Mrs. Clifton G. (Fonstad, Carmenza O.) - Francesco, John, 1984 April 16; UA043.000379 (Box 13)
  - Franchi, William B. - Fried, Dr. Kenneth H., 1984 April 16; UA043.000380 (Box 13)
  - Fried, Dr. Marvin P. - Gailun, Dr. James Z., 1984 April 16; UA043.000381 (Box 13)
  - Gaines, Rev. Charles A. - Gariepy, Gerard B., 1984 April 16; UA043.000382 (Box 13)
  - Gariepy, Stephen P. - Gendreau, Dr. Alvin G., 1984 April 17; UA043.000383 (Box 13)
  - Gendron, David L. - Gilde, Marion F., 1984 April 17; UA043.000384 (Box 13)
  - Gildea, Dr. George - Glenn, Christine, 1984 April 23; UA043.000385 (Box 13)
  - Glenn, Gary - Goldenberg, Dr. Richard, 1984 April 23; UA043.000386 (Box 13)
  - Goldfarb, Dr. Burton - Gordon, Deborah, 1984 April 23; UA043.000387 (Box 13)
  - Goldstein, D and M, J - Kyers, Randolph, 1984 June 14; UA043.000388 (Box 12)
  - Gooch, Jennifer Duffield - Zukor, Kimberly Joi, 1984 June 15; UA043.000389 (Box 12)
  - Gordon, Denise - Grahn, Mrs. Robert, 1984 April 23; UA043.000390 (Box 13)
  - Grahn, Rupert - Greene, Dr. Thomas, 1984 April 23; UA043.000391 (Box 13)
  - Greene, Vaughn - Grossman, Harry, 1984 April 23; UA043.000392 (Box 13)
  - Grossman, Robert - Haavik, Harold, 1984 April 23; UA043.000393 (Box 13)
  - Haavik, Mrs. Harold - Halliwell, Mrs. Constance, 1984 April 23; UA043.000394 (Box 13)
  - Halliwell, John - Hallock, Donald, 1984 April 23; UA043.000395 (Box 13)
  - Hallock, Dr. G Vinton - Hansen, Dr. Marshall, 1984 April 23; UA043.000396 (Box 13)
  - Hansen, Mrs. Nancy - Harrison, Franklin, 1984 April 23; UA043.000397 (Box 13)
  - Harrison, George - Hayes, Mrs. Callie, 1984 April 23; UA043.000398 (Box 13)
  - Hayes, Dr. Charles - Helfand, Dr. Zolman, 1984 April 23; UA043.000399 (Box 13)
  - Helfant, Dr. Richard - Hersam, Richard, 1984 April 23; UA043.000400 (Box 13)
  - Hersch, Robert - Hillman, Stephen, 1984 April 23; UA043.000401 (Box 13)
  - Hills, Mrs. Barbara - Hoffner, John, 1984 April 23; UA043.000402 (Box 13)
  - Hofmann, Lucinda - Hopkins, Elwood, 1984 April 23; UA043.000403 (Box 13)
  - Hopkins, George - Howitt, Doran, 1984 April 23; UA043.000404 (Box 13)
  - Howland, Mrs. Chester - Hurst, M/M Stanley, 1984 April 23; UA043.000405 (Box 13)
  - Hurst, Mark - Isom, Harriet, 1984 April 23; UA043.000406 (Box 13)
  - Isom, O'Neal, Jr. - Jaslow, Richard, 1984 April 23; UA043.000407 (Box 13)
  - Jaspan, Dr. Robert - Johnson, Dr. R Stephen, 1984 April 23; UA043.000408 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Raymond - Kadish, Dr. Harold, 1984 April 23; UA043.000409 (Box 13)
  - Kadish, Lynne - Karp, Stephen, 1984 April 23; UA043.000410 (Box 13)
  - Karp, Steven C. - Keith, Roger S., 1984 April 30; UA043.000411 (Box 13)
  - Keith, Russell O. - Kerr, Robert J., 1984 April 30; UA043.000412 (Box 13)
  - Kerr, Susan A. - Kiniry, George M., 1984 April 30; UA043.000413 (Box 13)
  - Kiniry, Malcolm - Knight, Mrs. Lloyd W. (Marion F. Foster), 1984 April 30; UA043.000414 (Box 12)
  - Knight, Lois H. - Kozlowski, Dr. Mark A., 1984 April 30; UA043.000415 (Box 12)
  - Kozman, Robert - Laakso, Dr. William, 1984 May 3; UA043.000416 (Box 12)
  - Kyle, M and M, John K. - Pasternak, L.J., 1984 June 14; UA043.000417 (Box 12)
  - Laan, Bruno - Lanney, Nicholas A., 1984 April 30; UA043.000418 (Box 12)
  - Lamb, L Edward J. - Zwoden, Dr. Abram, 1984 June 15; UA043.000419 (Box 12)
  - Lanni, Dr. John P. - Lawrie, Mrs. Linda (Linda B. Chace), 1984 April 30; UA043.000420 (Box 12)